Swetcha: Okay, so hi, my name is Swetcha, and I'm the HRBP at A4G.
Swetcha: And I will be asking you questions to test your natural fitment, natural fitment and organizational fitment in our organization.
Harshita kerni: Okay.
Swetcha: Alright.
Swetcha: Okay.
Swetcha: What type of work or project feels hardest for you to manage, and how do you organize it so it doesn't feel overwhelming?
Harshita kerni: So, the work that, like, feel, feels harder is, like.
Harshita kerni: projects with multiple people, and that have tight, deadlines, it can be challenging, and I break the work into smaller tasks, and I firstly prioritize the tasks.
Harshita kerni: Which is the most important, and set clear timelines, and, track the progress regularly. And, this is how I make sure that the project keeps organized, and it is prevented from being, like, I prevent… like, this is how I prevent from being overwhelmed.
Swetcha: Okay.
Swetcha: Okay, in a remote or team-based work, what are some problems you've seen that show up and show up immediately, but cause trouble later?
Harshita kerni: Okay, so with the remote, like, opportunity, one common problem is that, there is, like, unclear roles or delayed communication.
Harshita kerni: like, when it is a on-site job, then we have… we work in the same office. So, we can clearly clear the doubts, any doubts and anything about the project. It is clear on spot. But with the, remote job, there is a slight delay of communication. So, but,
Harshita kerni: Like, it can be, like, create a little hurdle in the job, and…
Harshita kerni: Firstly, like, a small miscommunication can later be caused, like, misused or, cause the deadlines or confusion at, like that.
Harshita kerni: Like, I would address it by clarifying responsibility and setting timelines and regularly checking the progress.
Swetcha: Have you ever realized midway that a task that you were working on wasn't adding much value? What did you do then?
Harshita kerni: Like, in project coordination, or the particular project?
Swetcha: project coordination, anything. Like, you can use a past experience where you have experienced it. Anything works.
Harshita kerni: like, in my current job, I have realized that a task like this work is not adding much in my resume. So, like, I have checked the project goals and everything, but it is not adding much to my resume.
Harshita kerni: So… That is why I'm looking for better opportunities.
Swetcha: Alright, can you tell me something that is specific to project management that you may have experienced in your previous job that is more relevant to work than to you?
Harshita kerni: Sorry, can you repeat it again?
Swetcha: Okay, no problem, I'll just ask you.
Harshita kerni: Getting a call, like, that's why…
Swetcha: It's completely alright.
Swetcha: Hmm…
Swetcha: Okay.
Swetcha: Okay, how do you usually regain control when you start feeling overwhelmed?
Harshita kerni: So, when I start feeling overwhelmed, then I, like, firstly absorb the, like.
Harshita kerni: the thing that is, like, making me overwhelmed, and then I step back and prioritize the tasks, like, based on the urgency and impact. Then I break the work into smaller tasks, and set clear deadlines, and focus on one thing at a time.
Harshita kerni: This helps me to stay organized and regain my control.
Swetcha: What do people usually rely on you for?
Harshita kerni: people, like, usually rely on me for, like, the management and basically the communication, because I think I have a greater sense of communication, because also I've come from a psychology background, so people usually rely on me for communication and making sure that the, all the team members gets the, project
Harshita kerni: deadlines and tasks completely well, and I'm also comfortable taking responsibility when there is a problem and finding practical solutions.
Swetcha: Tell me about a responsibility that you took that lasted overtime, not just one-time tasks, and how did you ensure that it got completed properly?
Harshita kerni: Okay, so one responsibility, like, I've handled over a long, like, a… I've handled over a longer period
Harshita kerni: the responsibility that I've handled for a longer period was managing ongoing projects and related tasks with coordination, and I made sure it stayed on track by setting priorities.
Harshita kerni: And following up regularly, tracking, like, deadlines, and reviewing the progress.
Harshita kerni: Which helped me…
Harshita kerni: Which helped me to make… ensure that the work was completely… completed properly, and rather than treating it on a non… on a one-time task.
Swetcha: Okay. And when you're unsure whether something is working or not, how do you check?
Harshita kerni: Okay, so… I…
Harshita kerni: like, usually check the actual reason against the expected outcome, and then I review the progress, and I look for the gaps that… what are the hurdles, and
Harshita kerni: take feedbacks from the, like, people that are involved, and I also… some, something is, like, if something is not working, then I identify the reason and make, changes quickly.
Swetcha: Now we'll move on to the organizational fitment round.
Swetcha: Okay, so… Okay.
Swetcha: Who is the hardest type of person? What is the hardest type of person for you to work with?
Harshita kerni: Okay, so I think the hard… it gets hard when, like, there is a miscommunication that happens, and when the people do not understand the task or the motive of the task clearly, and the people that don't take responsibility for their task.
Harshita kerni: But I try to understand the reason first, and I make sure that they understand the task well, and I communicate clearly, and set expectations so that we can work effectively together.
Swetcha: Oh.
Swetcha: What part of change do you struggle with the most?
Harshita kerni: like, the part of change that I struggle with the most is, like, adjusting quickly with priorities changing suddenly. But I, like, try to stay flexible and understand the new priorities, and reorganize my tasks accordingly.
Swetcha: What kind of problems do you enjoy thinking about?
Harshita kerni: So, the kind of problems that I enjoy thinking about is, like, solving practical problems.
Harshita kerni: Especially when there are multiple priorities and multiple people involved. Like, I like to understand the root cause and finding a simple solution, and then I make sure that the same problem doesn't happen again.
Swetcha: When you mess up, who's the first person you usually tell?
Harshita kerni: Okay, so when I mess up, so I usually make sure that the first, person, that I inform is the person that is responsible, or, like, the team members, and if it's a bigger issue, or, or it needs a decision, then I, escalate it to the… escalate it to my manager.
Harshita kerni: Or the project lead with the situation and a possible solution.
Swetcha: Okay, that is it for my questions. Thank you so much, Harshita. Sushma, would you like to ask anything?
Sushma: No, no. Harshita got to know your story, like, you know…
Sushma: The decision that you would like to move?
Sushma: Withdraw from your present internship, I have all the story behind that.
Sushma: So, any questions that you would like to ask us from your end?
Harshita kerni: Okay, so I'm, like, very interested in, like, my, according, about my career in project management. So, I would like to ask, like, will this, internship help me build my experiences and skills and all?
Sushma: Definitely, 100%. So, if you can able to learn and grow.
Sushma: You're ready to learn and grow, there is great opportunities. You can learn the foundation of project management, and beyond that.
Sushma: As well. But, the thing is that, here we are not… Spoon-feeding the inerts.
Sushma: So if you go out, you can see that most of the interns, like, you know.
Sushma: always, used to wait for the, TL thing, TL, you know, when TL said, they will say, what to do, what not to do. But here, it's not like that.
Sushma: So, you know, you will be given a two to three teams to handle the project management. You will be given a conceptual understanding what, can be done.
Sushma: So, how can return is something that you have to…
Sushma: fix that. So, here, the platform, here you can…
Sushma: explore many things, propose, you know, start initiatives, many things. We welcome your ideas and suggestions, you know? Here,
Sushma: what are the innovative thoughts to develop these structures and processes? You're welcome for that. And if anything that, should be to… or any tool, exploring is required. So we increase the learning by the end. Self-learning is very important here.
Sushma: So, you have to learn, and you have to put to the… what are the learnings that you're gaining in the concept and understanding from the operational leaders. You have to put those learnings into actions. Then only you can see the results.
Sushma: So…
Harshita kerni: Will I, like, like, in my, current, internship, like, they usually force us to use our personal information, like our number, for the company's benefit. So, will I…
Sushma: Here, there is, like, you know, if you have to, there is no chance for you to communicate with outsiders, initially.
Sushma: If it is required, there is a company's mail list there.
Sushma: So you can communicate through that. Even we HRs also, even if you see the HRs, our first… first, contact of communication from source LinkedIn only. So, we… whatever you got from the LinkedIn, you know, Google Form.
Sushma: link, or even interview link that received you from Nitin's LinkedIn account. That is not… but actually weHRs are using for the purpose of hiring.
Harshita kerni: Okay.
Sushma: After that, just, you know, if there are any phone call, even the phone calls also, we are implementing the CRM tool. If you're not a team member for project manage, like, you're not a team member for marketing or growth or some other team, CB team.
Sushma: as of now, so that, you know, if it is required to communicate with prospects or partner sponsors, they will be having a CRM tool. From that, they can… because now the team is building that customized CRM tool.
Sushma: So you're not required. So, if you're hesitate to do that, you can, you know, directly inform to the company that, you know, I'm not comfortable of using my phone number or mail ID for the outsiders.
Harshita kerni: Yes, because, like, they… in my current internship, they make us, call hundreds of people per day, and as you can see, my contact numbers has already 11 spam reports.
Sushma: While they're using your account, I got to know that, the console be something,
Sushma: Something like, consultant form, recruitment consultant form, right?
Harshita kerni: Yes, my job is, basically, I don't think so, it's project management. I think it's more of a recruitment or consulting type of job, so that's why…
Sushma: Why did you apply project management in general? What did they mention in the job description?
Harshita kerni: They mentioned about, like, our projects are called projects only, but we have to recruit, freelancers and all for this job. So, main task is recruitment.
Harshita kerni: So they mention us, and they don't mention us as the project managers, they mention us as project coordinators.
Sushma: That completely changes the role. Even the project coordinator, also, they change up the role and role and responsibilities, all right there.
Harshita kerni: That is why it is not building my resume or my skills.
Sushma: Are you current? Okay, I have to take two things also, Swetch I forgot to take, actually. I just got to remember just now.
Sushma: Tell me how your career aspiration will be aligned to this internship or to this organization.
Harshita kerni: like, I'm looking to move forward, like, working with you, like, I was also going to ask if there any, PPO offered after this internship, and as, like, I want to build a strong career in project management, so that's why.
Sushma: Okay, answering to your question, if you're looking for PPVO opportunities.
Sushma: I'm not sure about that, you will get a PPV opportunity here, firstly.
Harshita kerni: Okay.
Sushma: It may or may not chances will be there.
Sushma: For instance, in your 6 months of commitment of internship tenure.
Sushma: If you perform very well and extraordinary, you will get a chance to extend
Sushma: And we may convert into consultant role.
Sushma: Okay?
Sushma: So, here… Meanwhile, if the organization, is, you know.
Sushma: Planning currently to, propose, or to initiate or roll out the fellowship program.
Sushma: If that is done in the 6 months, maybe…
Sushma: Like, you know, you will get a chance to explore the fellowship program with the same role, but fellowship program will be there.
Sushma: That is for next 6 months or 12 months, if you would like to continue, either 6 months or 12 months, it depends.
Sushma: It's your choice. So, after that, based upon the funds.
Sushma: that the organization is getting CSO funds.
Sushma: So that, you will get an opportunity for full-time.
Harshita kerni: Okay, sure.
Sushma: But it depends, because here it's a non-profit organization.
Sushma: But the organization is currently focusing,
Sushma: To raising, to raise the funds.
Sushma: But if we succeed to get the funds.
Sushma: Then definitely, like, you know, you can expect full-time opportunity.
Sushma: Reducing pay.
Sushma: But, meanwhile, I cannot assure that. Say, like, you know, after 6 months, immediately, you will get, you know, full-time role. I can't assure on that.
Sushma: After 6 months, maybe?
Sushma: You will get a chance of promoting a consultant role. From Intern to Consultant role will be… tag will be added to you.
Sushma: Or otherwise, a fellowship program is designed, so you will be, you know, getting a chance to explore our fellowship program.
Harshita kerni: Okay.
Sushma: Are you comfortable with this? Because I know that, are you currently studying? I just want to check your resume template.
Harshita kerni: No, I've completed my master's, like, in May 2026.
Sushma: Okay, in which one did you complete?
Harshita kerni: May.
Sushma: Me.
Sushma: Okay. Now, why are you not looking for full-time opportunities? Why you would like to take the intern roles?
Harshita kerni: Because, like, I live in Jammu, and I'm looking… there are much no, like.
Harshita kerni: corporate opportunities available here regarding project management, and I'm currently not, looking to relocate, so that is why I'm, looking to, like, looking for a remote opportunity. So, I think, remote jobs are not, like,
Harshita kerni: inclusive of the entry level, like, I don't have much experience of 1 or 2 years, so that is why I'm looking for an internship.
Sushma: Okay, so you already worked as a project management intern in J Beverages privately?
Sushma: Yes, that…
Harshita kerni: What's an internship?
Sushma: Can you please tell me, like, you know, the roles and responsibilities that you contributed there, and the insights and learnings you gained there?
Harshita kerni: So, basically, like, in, that organization, my main task was to, like, focus on supporting project coordination, like, from day-to-day execution, and I was coordinating with people, and also following up on pro- progressing, progressive…
Harshita kerni: like, on progress and maintaining records, and I'm, make sure that the work, like, was, completed within timeline. I, and I was main, like, my main goal was.
Harshita kerni: To communicate with the wholesalers and the, take, take up the, like.
Harshita kerni: Like, manage them, and… Also, to take up the client feedback and all.
Harshita kerni: And, like, to maintain the task according to that.
Harshita kerni: It was more focused on the wholesaler and the client relation.
Sushma: And project coordinator, you've worked at, Ishita Food Products?
Harshita kerni: Yes, it was a, like.
Harshita kerni: It was also a food, like, industry, and at there, also there, my role was mainly, like.
Harshita kerni: I was looking for… I was working as a project coordinator, and my responsibilities were coordinating with tasks, and communication with different people, and…
Harshita kerni: Like, following up with the work, and maintaining records, and, like.
Harshita kerni: this only, regarding this only. In food industry, the main, like, work of a project management is regarding the wholesaler, the, customer relation, and that.
Sushma: So, you've done a B and MA in economics. So, being economics student, why you would like to…
Sushma: Now, settle your career in project management.
Harshita kerni: So, I've also done a BA in psychology, so that is why I was more inclined to working in a 4G, organization, because it is a non-profitable organization, and it is working for, like, the welfare with the help of an AI.
Harshita kerni: And that is why I think, it fits, best with the, like, the goals that I am looking forward. And also, the economics, like, degree has taught me to.
Harshita kerni: Build an analytical thinking and, like, resource allocation, and also it helps… helped me with decision making.
Harshita kerni: Which is relevant to project management, and during my internship, I also realized that I enjoy planning, coordinating with people, and solving problems, so that is why I'm looking forward to build my career in project management.
Sushma: According to you, can you please, you know, let me know what's your understanding about project management?
Harshita kerni: Okay, so, like, project management includes, like, making sure that the project is completed well within the given timelines, with the help of the coordination with the team, and, like, it involves setting goals, managing people and resources, and taking
Harshita kerni: The, timelines, also identifying the risk and solving prob… issues that… that might occur within the
Harshita kerni: Project. And also, it ensures that the quality is met well, and the basic outcome of the project is achieved.
Sushma: Alright.
Sushma: What's your last known stipend, like, your current stipend?
Harshita kerni: My current stipend over here is, like, 10K.
Sushma: And get a month.
Harshita kerni: Yes.
Harshita kerni: So… but the stipend is good according to, like, the internship market, but the, vision and the skills that… and the experience, that I'm looking for, I'm not getting from this job. So, that is why.
Sushma: All right.
Sushma: So, do you have any expectations for your stipend?
Harshita kerni: I have expectations for, skills and experience, like, I'm, I'm… I don't think I will, like, if you, like, in this organization, if I… even if I'm getting less, but the experience and the skills that I'm looking for will go with… with my goal.
Harshita kerni: With a line with my feet.
Sushma: Alright.
Sushma: Oh…
Sushma: So, are you comfortable with the stipend structure that which I explained yesterday?
Harshita kerni: Yes, like, I am comfortable with it, and I think it will increase according to my experience and my skills.
Sushma: Sometimes 12 months, yeah.
Harshita kerni: Yes, yes, so I think it, like, it will work for me.
Sushma: Know what you're expecting from this internship.
Harshita kerni: So, like, the basic, reason that I'm working here, like.
Harshita kerni: it, like, I am a big supporter of mental health and everything, and everything that supports the welfare of people and all, and the basic, motto of this organization, like, attracted to me, attracted me to… towards working here, and one of the reasons, that I'm interested is that I gen… Generally also
Harshita kerni: Preach about mental well-being and, initiatives that support people's over, overall welfare.
Harshita kerni: And I also like that this organization connects with, connects technology with human well-being and social impact.
Sushma: Where are you from?
Harshita kerni: I'm from Jammu.
Sushma: And what were your father, mother, two, and siblings?
Harshita kerni: So, my father, like, the Ishida food products that I have worked in, it is my father's business, like, it is of food and the manufacturing of spices and all.
Harshita kerni: And my brother also works there, and I've also worked there, like, last year, like, as I've mentioned in my resume.
Harshita kerni: And currently, I'm looking to build a career of my own, and to become independent, so that's why I'm…
Harshita kerni: I've gained some experience, like, working there, and then I've worked at Jay Beverages, and then I'm, like, looking for opportunities remote.
Sushma: Do you have an Interviews or offers in pipeline?
Harshita kerni: like, currently, with this interview, I've also given an interview with another organization, but I'm not, looking to work with them, because, I don't think so their, goals, like, they're… that is also not, project management, like.
Harshita kerni: of…
Harshita kerni: from the core, the roles that are aligned with this job is not related to project management, so…
Harshita kerni: I have not, accepted their offer.
Sushma: If you got shortlisted here,
Sushma: Can we consider that you're an emitter channel?
Harshita kerni: Sorry?
Sushma: Are you a limited joiner, if you got shortlisted?
Harshita kerni: Yes, I've told that, like, I'm looking to switch my job, and if I am selected, I can join immediately.
Sushma: I think, from your current, internship, is there any specific notice period that you need to show?
Sushma: Or designation acceptance.
Harshita kerni: No.
Sushma: You can just, you know, inform them and leave the internship immediately.
Harshita kerni: Yes, because my fellow members that have joined with me, most of them has left, and they have joined other organizations, so I can switch as well.
Sushma: Alright.
Harshita kerni: They will just not provide us with the experience certificate, because the 6-month tenure is not completed, but I can switch to other job immediately. There is no…
Sushma: After 6 months, you got relays, after 1 end of month, that is not allowing… Yes.
Harshita kerni: Yes, I think one month is enough to understand that.
Sushma: Yeah, Yeah, that's it from my end, I think.
Sushma: Swetcha, do you want to add anything?
Swetcha: No, no thanks, Ishma.
Sushma: Okay, so we will let you know, Harshita, just drop your contact number, email address, and phone number in the chat box. If you got shortlisted, so you will get, you will hear from us.
Sushma: For the operational route.
Sushma: Maybe tomorrow, doctor tomorrow?
Sushma: If not, then, you know, Our concern that we just move with someone else.
Harshita kerni: Okay.
Harshita kerni: Sure.
Harshita kerni: So I have to write it over the chart.
Sushma: Yeah, yeah.
Harshita kerni: Yeah.
Sushma: Alright, so thank you, have a nice day, happy Sunday.
Harshita kerni: Same to you.
Sushma: Yeah.
Harshita kerni: Thank you.
Swetcha: However…
Harshita kerni: Bye-bye.
Sushma: Bye-bye.
Harshita kerni: Bye.